<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyUni</string>
    <string name="title_activity_university_details">UniversityDetails</string>
    <string name="university_detail1" formatted="false">
        The University of Arizona is a public land-grant research university in Tucson, Arizona.\n

        Founded in 1885 by the 13th Arizona Territorial Legislature, it was the first university in the Arizona Territory. \n

        The university is classified among "R1: Doctoral Universities – Very High Research Activity".\n

        Avg cost after aid is $16K \n

        Graduation rate is 64% \n

        Acceptance rate is 87% \n

        Arizona is a great state for international students looking for affordable and simple academic needs.\n

        Now that we have covered most of the top universities in Arizona,
        you can choose the one that fits your academic needs.\n

        Arizona is generally a safe place to live, but like any state, there are areas that may have higher crime rates than others.\n

        Some safe places are considered Oro Valley and Florence.

    </string>
    <string name="university_detail2" formatted="false">
        The University of Florida is a public land-grant research university in Gainesville, Florida.\n

        It is a senior member of the State University System of Florida.\n

        The university traces its origins to 1853 and has operated continuously on its Gainesville campus since September 1906.\n

        Avg cost after aid is $3679 \n

        Graduation rate is 88% \n

        Acceptance rate is 30% \n

        Quality Education: The top universities in Florida pay special attention to international students.\n

        They have specialised programs that would suit the educational demands of students from all over the world.\n

        Better Living Lifestyle: Florida is a place that is known for its nightlife, events, theme parks, and cuisine.
        Unlike the myth around Florida real estate being dirt cheap, Florida is truly a low-tax state.\n

        One key feature of the state\'s tax system that bolsters affordability is the lack of a state income tax.\n

        In Florida, residents don\'t have to part with any portion of their earnings due to state taxes.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail3" formatted="false">
        New York University is a private research university in New York City.\n
        Chartered in 1831 by the New York State Legislature,
        NYU was founded in 1832 by a group of New Yorkers led by Albert Gallatin as a non-denominational all-male institution near City Hall based on a curriculum focused on a secular education.\n

        Avg cost after aid is $40K \n

        Graduation rate is 85% \n

        Acceptance rate is 13% \n

        Scholarships and grants are types of financial aid you don\'t have to pay back. \n
        NYU offers or recognizes many scholarship options, including programs for new students, current NYU undergraduates, and scholarships from outside sources. \n
        In addition, NYU schools and colleges award their own scholarships.

        We don\'t have minimum score requirements,\n
        but competitive applicants will receive: 100 and above on the TOEFL iBT. 130 and above on the Duolingo English Test. 7.5 and above on the IELTS Academic.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail4" formatted="false">
        The University of Michigan (U-M, UMich, or simply Michigan) is a public research university in Ann Arbor, Michigan.\n
        Founded in 1817, it is the oldest institution of higher education in the state.\n
        The university consists of nineteen colleges and offers 250 degree programs at the undergraduate and graduate level across various liberal arts and STEM disciplines.\n
        It is the largest university by enrollment in the state of Michigan, with over 52,000 students as of 2023.
        It is one of the earliest American research universities and is a founding member of the Association of American Universities.\n
        The university is classified among "R1: Doctoral Universities – Very High Research Activity" according to the Carnegie Classification of Institutions of Higher Education.\n
        In 2021, it ranked 3rd among American universities in research expenditures according to the National Science Foundation. The university is accredited by the Higher Learning Commission.
        Avg cost after aid is $17K \n

        Graduation rate is 93% \n

        Acceptance rate is 20% \n

        The cost of living in Michigan is 3% lower than the national average.\n
        Housing is 13% lower than the national average, while utilities are 0% .\n
        When it comes to basic necessities such as food and clothing, groceries are around 1% higher than in the rest of the country, while clothing costs 1% higher.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail5" formatted="false">
        The University of Calgary is a public research university located in Calgary, Alberta, Canada.\n
        The University of Calgary started in 1944 as the Calgary branch of the University of Alberta, founded in 1908, prior to being instituted into a separate, autonomous university in 1966.\n
        Avg cost after aid is $17K \n

        Graduation rate is 93% \n

        Acceptance rate is 20% \n
        Calgary has the lowest cost of living of most Canadian cities such as Montreal, Toronto, Ottawa and Vancouver.\n
        It also offers affordable student accommodation including student housing, private apartments and university halls.\n
        Each type of student accommodation in Calgary has its unique offers.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail6" formatted="false">
        The University of California, Los Angeles is a public land-grant research university in Los Angeles, California, United States.\n
        Its academic roots were established in 1881 as a normal school then known as the southern branch of the California State Normal School. \n
        Avg cost after aid is $12K \n

        Graduation rate is 92% \n

        Acceptance rate is 11% \n

        Los Angeles County has 88 incorporated cities, one of which is Los Angeles.\n
        Los Angeles has at least 114 named neighborhood, one of which is Westwood.\n
        UCLA has its own zip code, 90095; some of the outskirts of the campus are in Westwood\'s zip code, 90024.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail7" formatted="false">
        The University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign is a public land-grant research university in Champaign, Illinois, and Urbana, Illinois.\n
        It is the flagship institution of the University of Illinois system and was founded in 1867.

         Avg cost after aid is $15K \n

        Graduation rate is 85% \n

        Acceptance rate is 60% \n

        Illinois is home to the best universities.\n
        These universities are widely recognised and offer a range of diverse courses and enhanced learning experiences.\n

        With a large part of the student body classified as international (59% of grad students and 24% of undergrad students),
        Illinois Institute of Technology is one of the few colleges with the most Indian students in the USA.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail8" formatted="false">
        The University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign is a public land-grant research university in Champaign, Illinois, and Urbana, Illinois.\n
        It is the flagship institution of the University of Illinois system and was founded in 1867.

         Avg cost after aid is $15K \n

        Graduation rate is 85% \n

        Acceptance rate is 60% \n

        Illinois is home to the best universities.\n
        These universities are widely recognised and offer a range of diverse courses and enhanced learning experiences.\n

        With a large part of the student body classified as international (59% of grad students and 24% of undergrad students),
        Illinois Institute of Technology is one of the few colleges with the most Indian students in the USA.
    </string>
    <string name="university_detail9" formatted="false">
        The University of Austin is a private nonsectarian liberal arts university located in Austin, Texas.\n
        In October 2023, the university received its certification to operate as a degree granting university from the Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board.\n
        Address: 522 Congress Ave. STE 300, Austin, TX 78701, United States.\n
        Avg cost after aid is $15K \n

        Graduation rate is 85% \n

        Acceptance rate is 60% \n

        Tuition fees for international students are typically higher than for in state residents.\n
        It\'s important to research the specific university or college you plan to attend and consider factors such as housing options, meal plans, and other living expenses.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail10" formatted="false">
        The University of North Carolina at Charlotte is a public research university in Charlotte, North Carolina.\n
        UNC Charlotte offers 24 doctoral, 66 master\'s, and 79 bachelor\'s degree programs through nine colleges.\n
        It is classified among "R2: Doctoral Universities – High research activity".\n
        Avg cost after aid is $17K \n

        Graduation rate is 64% \n

        Acceptance rate is 79% \n

        North Carolina is home to educational excellence.\n
        We have 52 colleges and universities, including three Tier 1 research universities, and the third largest community college system in the U.S. North Carolina\'s education institutions award over 25,000 STEM degrees annually.

        While the Tar Heel State has minor setbacks when it comes to daily quality of life,
        the benefits of living in North Carolina far outweigh the bad! With beautiful outdoor views/activities,
        great job opportunities, delicious food and rich history to explore,
        the good times never get old when living in North Carolina.
    </string>

    <string name="university_detail11">
        The University of Windsor is a public research university in Windsor, Ontario, Canada. \n
        It is Canada\'s southernmost university.\n
        It has approximately 17,500 students. \n
        The university was incorporated by the provincial government in 1962 and has more than 150,000 alumni.\n
        The University of Windsor\'s Acceptance Rate is 60%.\n
        This means that out of every 100 applicants, 60 will be offered admission to the University.\n
        Windsor ranks 38 out of 50 best Canadian cities for international students. Windsor has seen a rapid increase in the amount of international students in the city over the last few years,
        but a recent list published by Clever Canadian said Windsor is the 38 best place for international students in a list of 50.\n
        It has been ranked as one of the top universities in Canada and one of the top universities in the world.\n
        There are over 200 programs offered at this university.\n
        The University of Windsor also has an international student population with over 5,000 students from more than 100 countries.\n
        Also called Rose City and The City of Roses,
        Windsor is further renowned for its beautiful parks and gardens,
        which are nestled along its waterfront.
    </string>
</resources>